when we create the technology for
massive collaboration we unleash the
full potential of humanity on our
complex challenges every individual is
not only welcome but empowered with the
tools to find and carry out their own
unique contribution tools that will
allow groups with purpose to find their
people that allow individuals to find
ways to help that inspire them allows
them to use their unique talents
intelligence and challenges to best
serve themselves their communities and
their causes tools like a massive
communication tool this is our first
project called the idea cafe linked in
the description project management tools
available for free to everyone tasks
assignments and volunteer tools group
finding problem-solving tools issue
resolution for constant improvement with
each iteration of every tool we create
empowering people to tell us what's not
working for them so we can work on
improving it voting for features or
leaders as needed tools for everything
we can imagine as individuals and
collectively with each new iteration
bringing improvement to everyone and
every group with technology for massive
collaboration we can allow everyone to
contribute in their own way and have a
powerful collective result then we can
create a world for everyone by allowing
everyone to create a world for
themselves